wiaawi.org 2015-11-12

# Wisconsin Interscholastic Athletic Association Privacy Policy

Wisconsin Interscholastic Athletic Association Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy tells you about WIAA’s policies and practices for the collection, use and disclosure
of information we collect about you through our sites and services, including the website
www.wiaawi.org. By using our sites and services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and
you consent to the processing of information about you as described here.
Information we collect
Information you give to us.
When you complete an on-line official’s licensing application we ask you for the following
information:
     •    Credit card information
     •    Name and address
     •    Email address and telephone number
Information we collect when you use our sites and services.
We may collect information about the way you interact with our sites, services, content and
advertising, including computer, browser and connection information, statistics on page views,
traffic to and from our sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information.
We may obtain information from or about you in other ways. For example, we may verify user
information with a service provider. Also, you may send us correspondence, testimonials, photos,
blogs, writings, customer satisfaction surveys or customer service communications.
How we use information
Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient and
customized experience. We may use the information we collect to:
     •    provide the services and customer support you request
     •    resolve disputes, collect fees and troubleshoot problems
     •    prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities and enforce our policies
     •    customize, measure and improve our sites, services and advertising
     •    tell you about services and opportunities that may be of interest to amateur sport officials
          and service updates and promotional offers based on your communication preferences and
     •    compare information for accuracy and verify it with third parties.
How we share information
Except as disclosed in this Privacy Statement, we do not sell, trade, rent, or otherwise retransmit
any personally identifiable information we collect online unless we have your permission. From time
to time, we may be required to provide personally identifiable information in response to court

order, subpoena, or government investigation. We also reserve the right to report to law
enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful. We may release
personally identifiable information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary or to
protect the rights, property and safety of others and ourselves.
We may share aggregate information about our users with certain third parties. This information
shows user activity as a whole rather than on an individual basis and cannot be used to individually
identify you. We use this information to help our partners and funders better understand our
services and also to report on public interest in the site.
Security
Your information is stored on our servers located in the United States. We treat data as an asset
that must be protected and use tools (encryption, passwords, physical security, etc.) to protect your
personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, as you probably know,
third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications, and other
users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the site. Therefore,
although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect,
that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.
Third Parties
Except as otherwise expressly included in this Privacy Policy, this document addresses only the use
and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to others,
different rules may apply to their use or disclosure of the information you disclose to them. WIAA
does not control the privacy policies of third parties, and you are subject to the privacy policies of
those third parties where applicable. We encourage you to ask questions before you disclose your
personal information to others.
Privacy Policy Updates
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this site. Changes take
effect 30 days after they are posted to the site. This policy was last updated effective 5/1/2013
Questions
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this policy, please contact us at:
Wisconsin Interscholastic Athletic Association
5516 Vern Holmes Drive
Stevens Point, WI 54482              Phone (715) 344-8580      Email: jgralla@wiaawi.org
